http://www.floydcountytimes.com/site/privacy.html

Pikeville, KY
(41501)
Today
Generally sunny despite a few afternoon clouds. High 66F. Winds light and variable..
Tonight
Cloudy. Low 49F. Winds light and variable.
Home
This privacy notice discloses privacy practices for (ANI) www.appalachiannews-expressky.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it is shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside Appalachian Newspapers, Inc., other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. place an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about subscription specials, new products or services, or changes to this policy.You may opt out of any future contacts at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email at: jvanderbeck@news-expressky.com or 606-437-4054:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data. SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Whenever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for https at the beginning of the address page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are given access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact the Business Office immediately via telephone at 606-437-4054 or email the publisher at jvanderbeck@news-expressky.com RegistrationIn order to use portions of this website, a user must complete a subscription form. This subscription form requires certain information (such as name, address, telephone and email address). This information is used to contact you about services/products on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender and age) about yourself, but it is not required. OrdersWe request information when orders are placed in several locations on our site (such as subscription, classified ads, etc.). To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and home address) and financial information (like credit card, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, well use the information to contact you. CookiesWe use cookies on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitors hard drive to help us improve your access and identify repeat visitors to our site. For example, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Some of our business partners (for example: advertisers) may use cookies on our site. However, we have no access or control over these cookies.We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google's privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:(a) https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome);(b) https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences (Firefox);(c) http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera);(d) https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies (Internet Explorer);(e) https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari); and(f) https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy (Edge).Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of many websites, including our Site. Some features of the Site may cease to be available to you. SharingWe share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.We may use an outside shipping company to mail photos and other products, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your orderWe sometimes partner with outside parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. Interest-Based AdvertisingAdvertising. This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy LinksOur website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. Surveys & ContestsOccasionally, our site requests information via surveys, contests or for news items (such as People You Should Know). Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose your information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and home address) and demographic information (such as zip code, age, etc.). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. News items will be used for editorial news content that may be published in the printed Appalachian News Express.
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesKentucky governor defends order to close schoolsFather, daughter facing felony charges after custody investigationWilliams: 'I'm mad as hell'Appeal blocking PFD from providing emergency servicesTime to turn the page: Long-time FC Library employee retiringFloyd superintendent discusses moves made at recent meetingBeverly to fight in Kansas CityIndictment: Business owner made millions charging clients for services paid for by MedicaidOne Kentucky city good, one poor in terms of single livingP’burg to open hoops season in 15th Region All ‘A’ Classic
Images
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Stocks
Market Data by TradingView
© Copyright 2020 Floyd Chronicle & Times, 129 Caroline Ave. Pikeville, KY | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
